(indistinct chatter)
(cameras snapping)
Ah.
Hey, are you playing
in the game?
Uh, no, just him.
It's Paper Boi.
Oh, okay.
Well...
I think Lowrider magazine
wanted to talk to him.
Let me see if I can find
someone, one minute.
Cool.
Ah.
This gonna be awesome, boy.
Yo, it's time
to show these fools
why I'm a legend at two games.
I'm thinking, what?
MVP Honors.
Oh.
Yeah, you were pretty good
back in the day.
(scoffs)
Back in the day?
What?
I'm still fire.
Me and Darius be going to
the YMCA.
I still be...
* smashing it
(chuckles)
What ever happened to the old,
uh, running shoe place?
Oh, man, that place
was dope, wasn't it?
-Yeah.
-They shot it up though.
Dang.
I mean, niggas started trying
to call charging, man.
It was all bad.
Yeah.
(basketball bouncing)
You should go ahead
and interview me now
'cause I'ma be MVP
of this thing.
I'm sorry, what?
I sa--I--I said that you should
interview me 'cause I'ma...
play good today.
Oh.
(exhales)
Hey, you Valencia Joyner, right?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I see you do them
interviews on TV all the time.
And you are...
gorgeous!
(chuckles)
Thank you.
So what's good?
You...wanna interview me?
You know, I'll tell you
my whole life story.
Are you playing
in the game later?
Yup.
All right, you got me.
I'm a rapper.
(chuckles)
You may have heard of me.
Paper Boi.
I do that song.
-* Paper Boi, Pap--
-Oh, I know who you are.
You're the guy
who shot someone.
See what--
see, well,
it ain't really
happen like that.
You know what I'm saying?
The Internet,
they just run with stories, so.
So you need to
get to know the real me.
-Oh, yeah?
-Oh, yeah, yeah.
Look, I'll even let you
interview me
somewhere fly like Benihanas.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, that sound good, right?
I don't know.
My audience isn't into
the whole gangster thing.
I'm not really either.
(blows raspberry)
Gangster? I see.
No, baby, you got me
all wrong, man.
Look, I'm a gentleman first.
(chuckles)
That's why you need to
get to know...
-Hey, Val, I need to--
-Me.
I need to prep you
for the half-time segment.
-Rosalyn has a few questions.
-Okay.
-Well, you have fun at the game.
-Well, hold up, wait.
See--
Damon Wayans-looking nigga.
(sighs)
(funk music)
*
Who's that?
Val Joyner.
You know her?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, she cute.
(mutters)
Yeah.
-Justin Bieber!
(girls shouting)
Oh, shit,
it's Justin Bieber.
(cameras snapping)
-Yeah, boy!
-Hey, Justin, right here.
Hey, Justin, right here!
-Hey!
-Justin!
I'm surprised
he even showed up, man.
What is the deal
with this nigga, man?
What do you mean?
Like, why everybody
always going crazy over him?
He can sing.
He can dance.
Girls think he's cute.
I don't know.
Man, that shit weird to me.
Hey, you that nigga that blew
that other nigga's brains out.
Cool.
Justin!
Over here!
It's cool.
VALENCIA: So hey, Justin,
how are you?
It's good to see you.
You look like you're ready
for the game.
And I--
(laughs)
I'm gonna dunk on a bitch!
ALFRED: I don't like this nigga.
I don't know,
he's kind of funny.
I mean, he's hot right now.
You should work with him.
I mean, speaking as
your manager, you know.
Just 'cause you dressed
like a 6th grader
don't make you my manager, man.
Hey, we're starting soon,
so you should get dressed.
-Cool.
-Locker room is this way.
Thank you.
-Hey, where you gonna be at?
-I don't know.
I'm probably gonna try and find
some corner to hang out in,
you know.
After the game,
I'll just find you.
All right.
(scoffs)
Hey, Alonzo.
Alonzo.
Alonzo, behind you.
Why, you little sneak,
you can't say hello?
(kisses and laughs)
Oh, I...
I don't--I don't think you...
mean to...
Oh, yeah, you're surprised
to see me, I'm sure.
Yeah, well, I'm back
from the dead again.
You know, I've been doing that
my whole career, so.
Was that your client
back there?
Uh, yeah.
That's--that's Paper Boi.
Oh, right.
I've heard of that.
So, uh, are you still
at CSA or did you go...
(coughs)
independent now?
I...
I'm independent.
(mumbles)
I think, um...
MAN: I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm sorry, ma'am, you--
you can't smoke that in here.
(sighs)
Okay.
So, uh, you're
coming upstairs, right?
I mean, all the other agents
and such are there.
So come on.
And I am gonna smoke up there,
like, I don't care
what that guy says about it.
EARN: Yeah.
JANICE: These days,
it is all about management.
I mean, the money is drying up
in all the old markets.
I mean, it's important to keep
what you have, is what I think.
I mean, you know
Alan Greengate, right?
He's the--he's the guy
who represents all those
athletes who want
to become actors.
I mean, he should be in here.
He'll tell you that I'm right.
Seriously.
He knows.
Whoa, whoa.
Where you going?
You need a pass
to get in here.
I-I didn't know--
I thought--
You playing
in the game or something?
You really don't think
that we're gonna wear
those ugly VIP laminates
that you guys sent out
on our chest, right?
Just let him through.
I mean, we--
we all don't want
to be at this thing.
Come on.
(yawns)
(children yelling in distance)
(dogs barking in distance)
(dramatic music plays on TV)
*
In the development
of the SOCP Dagger,
I spent several years
developing prototypes.
Well, it's got a
little more kick than the 9.
(gun clicks)
This your first time shooting?
No.
No, it'll be fine.
I'll take that one.
All right.
(country music over radio)
Oh, yeah,
and two boxes of bullets.
All right.
There you go.
All right,
thank you, my friend.
-Have fun.
-Uh-huh.
(indistinct chatter)
(hip-hop bass thudding)
(urine splashing)
ALFRED: This kid is a mess, man.
Yeah, he crazy.
Man, I see him on TV
all the time wylin' out.
He can't even really dance,
ain't like he Chris Brown.
He just trying
to figure it out.
Whatever, man.
You getting real soft
these days.
(exhales)
(whistle blows)
(announcer speaking
indistinctly)
(cheering and clapping)
(cheering)
Hand down!
Man down!
JUSTIN: Nigga!
(gunshots)
(whistling)
(keypad beeps)
(machine whirs)
(gun clicking)
(gun cocks)
(gun firing)
(indistinct cheering)
-Come on, yeah.
-You don't want this now.
Come on.
Come on, man!
(cheers)
-I got Bieber, man.
-(scoffs)
All right?
I got Bieber.
-I'm in this for charity.
-Yeah, okay.
Well, then donate Bieber
to me then, all right?
-It's for the kids.
-I got Bieber, give him to me.
(indistinct cheers)
(cheers)
MAN: Do your thing, B!
(crowd groans)
Oh, you gonna dunk
on a bitch?
Aight, little nigga.
Aight.
Okay.
Oh, I left a bag of dicks for
you to eat in the locker room.
Well, your breath smell like
you already ate a bag yourself.
Well, that's okay, but
you can tell your mom to eat
-that bag of dicks, all right?
-Okay.
-Is that cool for you?
-Aight.
Is it too late
to say I'm sorry, man?
to get your hairline done?
How bout you hairline
deez nuts, nigga?
How bout that?
(whistle blows)
Let's go.
What you got?
-What you got?
-Ball.
Ball.
Nigga, give me the ball.
Nigger!
Thanks!
What you got?
Bout to whoop
your pomegranate ass.
This ain't Space Jam, nigga.
Play ball, let's go--
Shit.
(cheers)
Damn.
You broke in real life
and basketball.
(scoffs)
(guns firing)
(chuckles)
Yeah.
All right.
What do you think
you're doing?
(shouting)
What do you think you're doing?
Who? Me?
Shooting.
You can't shoot dogs.
What are you, a psycho?
Why not?
Listen, man, look,
the dogs from my neighborhood,
they're crazy.
They bite babies and--and--
I don't give a damn.
My kid could be in here.
You--you can't shoot a dog.
Well, why would I shoot
at a human target?
I mean, that's weird, right?
I mean, look at that one.
That's just
way too specific, man.
I don't care.
I--I'm not gonna let you
shoot a fucking dog in here.
-Hey.
-But--
He can shoot
whatever he wants.
You shoot at your racist targets
with no problem.
I saw you shoot at that one
with a Mexican holding a knife.
It's shameful.
America has taken so much.
No more.
A revolution
will rise from within.
Blood will spill.
(mumbles)
Well, I didn't say all that,
but, you know...
You ain't gonna shoot
no dog target.
MAN: You!
Let's go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey--hey, uh--
what--what did I do, man?
I told you the rules
before you came in here.
I ain't gonna let you
start no shit.
(country music over radio)
Oh.
Uh, you still have my ID.
Can I get the dog poster?
-Get the hell out.
-Okay.
(store entrance bell jingles)
(scoffs)
Yeah, definitely, I mean,
with the way things are going
nowadays, I mean,
you got to be careful about
-the deals you sign.
-Mm-hmm.
See, I tell my clients that
all the time.
Brand association
is important.
EARN: Yeah.
-Yeah, working in music,
you definitely got to
do it different.
I think that's why
John went to TV.
(polite laughter)
So hey, is--is your client
working with anyone
on the TV side?
'Cause I got
a few people looking
for that sort of thing,
ad-wise.
Um, my client's
interested in
anything that...
pays money.
-(laughter)
-Right.
Makes sense.
So who you with, ASA?
I'm independent.
Okay, well, take my card
and we should get together
'cause I have a lot
going on next year
and I want to make sure
I got good people on board.
Here, take mine as well.
Great.
Uh...
I--I ran out of cards here
so, like,
I'll just make sure to call both
of you guys.
-Okay.
-Yeah, that's great.
And--what's your name, again?
Just call me Earn, yeah.
-Earn, okay.
-Earn.
-Well, great to meet you, Earn.
-Yeah.
-Be in touch.
-It was great meeting you.
Yeah, it was really nice
meeting you guys.
Talk to you soon.
Same here, bye.
(lounge piano music playing)
(taps cards)
*
How much for a beer?
Oh, it's, uh, gratis.
Oh, uh, then I'll have
a Hennessy and Grand Marnier.
Yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
Here you go.
Hey, Janice.
Mm...
whiskey, straight up?
Uh, Bushmills,
not the cheap stuff.
I'm worth it.
(laughs)
(lighter flicks)
So...
you having fun yet?
(lighter snaps shut)
Yeah.
It's great up here.
I'm sure it is.
(clears throat)
Remember at the Grammys,
it was six years ago,
isn't that where
we first met?
Yeah, I think so.
-Yeah.
Yeah, you were just
a rookie in this thing.
Remember?
(laughs)
-Look at you now.
-(laughs)
I'm just happy
to be here, you know.
I--I remember I--I--
I told you that
loyalty was
really important, that, uh...
(clears throat)
the good ones are loyal
to their clients,
the great ones, though,
are loyal to their peers.
Yeah.
Yeah, okay.
(sighs)
(scoffs)
You know I don't work
for ASA anymore?
I didn't--
nah, I didn't know that.
Yeah, it's been really hard
for me in this business.
You know, coming in
as a woman, but...
(clears throat)
the last three years
have been even worse.
Sorry to hear that.
Yeah.
(scoffs)
Look,
I know it was you, Alonzo.
-What?
-(exhales)
I know you sold me out,
you faggot cocksucker!
-Whoa--
-What did you think I
wouldn't know it was you?
You've been avoiding me
the last three years!
You piece of shit.
You undercut me.
I had to hear from Gail--
fucking Gail--
that you were speaking
to my clients.
I know--I--
I'm sorry.
(laughs)
What is happening?
You screwed me over
and you thought I wasn't
gonna know it was you,
but I know!
I know, Alonzo.
Okay?
I know.
-No, no--
-Yeah, no-no.
It's all right.
It's okay. You thought
I was finished, but...
(clears throat)
I'm a survivor.
(laughs)
No, there must be--
-there's a mistake happening...
-Mm. Mm-mm.
Right now, there's
some sort of mistake.
Mm-mm--wipe that sharecropper
smile off your face.
You know what?
I am going to ruin you.
I'm gonna ruin you.
No matter where you go,
I'm gonna follow you.
I'm gonna be on you
and I am going to take back
everything--everything
that you--you stole from me.
(smooches)
I'm not Alonzo.
I'm gonna make sure
that you die homeless.
(indistinct cheering)
What you got, little nigga?
I'm still MVP, nigga.
I'm coming for that shit.
Alfred, I'm open on the block!
I'm open!
WOMAN: I love you, Justin!
-I know, bitch!
Alfred! Alfred!
Alfred!
(crowd reacts)
Hell no, nigga.
No!
(whistle blows)
(crowd groans)
(crowd shouting indistinctly)
-Bitch.
-Nigga!
(buzzer rings)
(crowd groans)
-Oh, you pushing now?
-Come on.
You push me while my back
is turned?
How bout I push you
that way, huh?
You put your hands on me,
nigga?
(both grumbling)
(crowd murmuring)
Don't nobody even like
your stupid-ass music.
Get your hand off my face.
(both groaning and straining)
You know what?
I'm gonna kill you, nigga.
I'm gonna kill you.
-I'm gonna kill you.
-Gonna kill you first.
Look, I'm drunk,
but this is ridiculous.
-You dumb--nasty!
-Give me that fucking shit!
(crowd jeering)
-I hate you, I hate you, I...
-I'm MVP, I'm MVP, I'm MVP...
-I hate you, nigga!
-I'm MVP!
(indistinct chatter)
(cameras snapping)
Hey, everybody.
I just want to say, um,
sorry about
what happened today.
It's not who I am.
I--I guess I been trying
to be so...cool lately
that I became something I'm not.
(crowd gasps)
Wait.
It's cool, it's cool.
This is me.
This is the real Justin.
I'm not a bad guy.
I actually love Christ.
I guess I've just been hanging
out with the wrong people.
(hip-hop music builds)
Which is why I want to sing
this new single
from my upcoming album,
"Justice."
(scattered cheers)
*
(Auto-Tuned)
* Girl
* You know what I did
(women cheer)
* Doesn't matter
* You know that
I'll always be better *
* Sometimes I'm crazy
and I know it *
I can't believe this nigga.
JUSTIN: * That's how I show you
that I care *
* Whatever I did, girl
Hey.
Crazy day, right?
(laughs)
Hey, look, I just want
to apologize
to people, you know,
for how I was acting.
Think they got
the wrong idea of me.
Maybe...
you can interview me sometime?
Get to know the real me.
(inhales)
Listen, I want
to give you some advice.
Play your part.
People don't want Justin
to be the asshole.
They want you
You're a rapper.
That's your job.
JUSTIN: * Whatever I did
doesn't matter *
* You know that I'll
always be better *
* Sometimes I'm crazy
and you know it *
*
Hey, man, how the game go?
(scoffs)
Terrible.
You ain't see that?
No, man, see what?
It don't even matter, man.
JUSTIN: * Whatever I do, girl,
just forget about it *
-What is wrong with you?
-Nothing.
Nothing.
Nothing, man.
Um, you want to
get out of here, man?
Yeah.
Yeah, man, let's do that.
* Everybody put your hands up
* Girl
* You know what I did
doesn't matter *
* You know that I'll
always be better *
* Sometimes I'm crazy
and you know it *
* That's how I show you
that I care *
* Whatever I did, girl,
forget about it *
* Whatever I say, girl,
just forget about it *
* Whatever I do, girl
* Just forget about it
all night long *
* Girl
* Whoa
(echoes)
Everybody put your hands up.
Clap 'em together.
Clap 'em together for me.
*
* Ooh, oh, na-na